SUMMARY

After many years in the I.T. Computer industry a shift in my career has led me to a new and successful sales career position in the renewable energy industry selling solar systems in homes all across south Florida.

As an Innovator and entrepreneur with over 25 years in business leadership. Experienced in all aspects of business formation, operation, finance, and management as well as a technical background in I.T. and Cyber Security. Visionary with deep skills in product analytics and launch. Effective motivator and communicator who identifies and leverages assets in team mates to reach maximum productivity and goals. Relentless optimist who believes there is no failure. Currently actively involved with St Pete Charity organization to help in raising funds for local charities on a regular basis.

SKILLS

- Creative thinking
- Innovator of products and services specializing in I.T. services
- Leadership
- Strong business principles and management principles as they pertain to development and innovation.
- Technical background in business analytics
- Motivator and team player with excellent written and communication skills
- Risk Taking
- Extremely entrepreneurial and thinking outside the box.

- Started businesses with own funds and secured investors.
- Strong Work Ethic
- A lot of hard work and long hours dedicated to launching new businesses and products.
- Early start to each day. Well before sunrise or send middle-of-the-night emails.
- Relentless when it comes to completing projects and following through on the work required to turn ideas and plans into sellable products.
- Sales driven
- customer satisfaction driven

EXPERIENCE

Solar Sales Consultant / Solarmax, LLC - Clearwater, FL

07/2018 - Current

- In home energy management consulting and solar sales.
- Co-op sales and coordination.
- HOA, Golf outings, Charity events, and home shows are all part of lead generation
- Solar sale with energy efficiency bundled co-op package that included: insulation, roofs, AC units, radiant barrier, heat recovery system, hot water heater jacket, pool pumps, AC units, and more...
- Consultative approach to home energy efficiency.
- Proven track record with 45% closing ratio
- Proven excellence in presentation and communication skills.
- Ability to outsell competition on value and value add over price.
- Ability to articulate the value of renewable energy and demonstrate the financial value as a "no brainer approach" to close sales.
- Consistently generate over \$ 50K per week revenue.
- Represented Solar systems and back up solutions from all name brand manufacturers.

- Merged my marketing company to help re-invent Centurion's marketing efforts and launch cyber security solution in the consumer market.
- Planned and executed a complete DRTV campaign and QVC.
- Secured a 4 star rating from PC Magazine.
- Featured in CIO best educational institutions security enterprise software.
- secured patent on our reboot restore technology.
- helped in re-structuring and re-capitalizing the company.
- cut costs and improved net revenues.
- responsible for all aspect of the business: sales, marketing, budgeting, software development, strategic planning and vision execution.

CEO / Computer Centers USA, Inc - Tampa, Florida

05/2007 - 09/2015

- Took the company from a small retail PC repair shop to an international service company specializing in remote PC repair.
- developed the Magic Flash Drive...a USB stick with software to clean and optimize your PC as well as a technical support button the instantly connected you to a USA based computer technician
- Secured a patent
- established relationships with all the major home shopping channels i.e. QVC, HSN, TSC, and Evine.
- Contracted QVC and HSN to handle remote tech support as part of a bundle for all PC's and Mac's sold on air.
- 24/7/365 days per year operation
- Took company from 60K per year revenue to over 4 Million.

Real Estate Developer / Self - Chicago, IL

03/2002 - 09/2006

- developed raw land into residential communities
- dealt with municipalities to get approval for developments
- planned, designed and executed two major residential communities with 20 plus homes in each.
- Managed contractors and subs
- Handled all sales and marketing efforts
- Handled all legal and accounting functions

CEO / Image Technology Solutions, Inc - Chicago, IL

05/1997 - 02/2002

- Founder
- started a new and innovative concept for computer hardware repair for fortune 500 companies
- Started express restore advance exchange repair within 24 hrs with 97% customer satisfaction.
- Secured contracts from customers such as: Enterprise Rent A Car, Budget, Alamo, Hertz, Autozone, Federal Express, Trans Union, Edward Jones, And more.
- Start up to 12 million in annual revenue.
- Managed two locations. Chicago, IL and Memphis, TN

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

De Vry Institute of Technology - Chicago Electronics Engineering

- Managed the design and patent of Cyber security software.
- Designed and patented USB software for PC repair
- Featured in CIO Magazine
- Secured 4 star rating with PC Magazine for our cyber security and ransomware protection software
- Convinced QVC and HSN to bundle my tech support with all PC sales sold on TV.